patauza.co.ke 2019-07-14

# Kenya jobs, cars, property, free classifieds and more - patauza.co.ke, daily deals

### General

This privacy policy describes the policy of www.PataUza.co.ke regarding the collection, use, storage, sharing and protection of your personal information ("Privacy Policy"). This Privacy Policy applies to the PataUza website ("Website"), regardless of how you access the Services, including access through mobile devices. In formal terms, PataUza is the data controller of your personal information.

### Scope and consent

By using www.PataUza.co.ke and related Services, you give explicit consent to PataUza for the collection, use, disclosure and retention of your personal information by us, as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

PataUza may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We advise you to read it regularly. Substantial changes to our Privacy Policy will be announced on our Website. The amended Privacy Policy will be effective immediately after it is first posted on our Website. This Privacy Policy is effective as of 23rd August 2010. 

### What personal information do we collect

You can visit our Website without registering for an account. When you decide to provide us with your personal information, you agree that such information is sent to and stored on our servers. We collect the following types of personal information: 

Information you provide to us: We collect and store any information you enter on our Website or that you provide to us when you use our Services. This information includes, but is not limited to: 

  * information that you provide to us when you register for an account or for the Services that you use including for example, your name, address, email address, telephone number or financial information;
  * additional information that you may provide to us through social media sites or third party Services;
  * information provided in the context of dispute resolution, correspondence through our Website or correspondence that is sent to us; and
  * information about your location and the location of your device, including your device's unique identifier information if you have enabled this service on your mobile device.

### How we use your personal information

You agree that we may use your personal information (see above) for the following purposes: 

  * to provide you access to our Services and Customer Support by means of e-mail or telephone;
  * to prevent, detect and investigate potentially prohibited or illegal activities, fraud and security breaches and to enforce our Terms of Use;
  * to personalize, measure and improve our Services, content and ads;
  * to contact you, by e-mail, push notification, text message (SMS) or by telephone, to inquire about our Services for the purpose of targeted marketing activities, updates, and promotional offers based on your message preferences (where applicable), or for any other purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy; and
  * to provide you with other services that you have requested, as described when we collected the information.

### Sharing information with and registration on social media sites

We may offer sign-on Services that enable you to access the Website or related websites with your login credentials. We can also offer Services that enable you to share information with third party social media websites, such as Facebook, Google Plus and Twitter.

If you provide us access to personal information stored on third party websites, the scope of access to this personal information shall vary per website and will be determined by both your own browser settings and your consent. If you wish to connect your third party account to your www.PataUza.co.ke account and you consent to us accessing the information in these third party accounts, you agree that we can collect, use and store information from this third party website in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We shall moreover - in our efforts to respect your privacy and to keep the website free of malicious persons or parties - not disclose your personal information to third parties without a court order or formal request from the government in accordance with applicable law, unless we believe in good faith that such disclosure (i) is necessary for the purpose of, or in connection with, any legal proceedings (including prospective legal proceedings), for the purpose of obtaining legal advice or is necessary for the purposes of establishing, exercising or defending legal rights, (ii) is necessary for the prevention or detection of crime, the capture or prosecution of offenders, or the assessment or collection of tax or duty, (iii) is requested by a body that performs public regulatory functions, or (iv) is otherwise authorized under the Data Protection Act.

### Information you share on www.PataUza.co.ke

Our Website allows users to share advertisements and other information with other users, thereby making this shared information accessible to other users. Since our Website also enables you to directly contact a buyer or seller, we recommend that you consider how you share your personal information with others. You are solely responsible for the personal information you share through our Website and therefore we cannot guarantee the privacy or security of the information shared by you with other users.

In case you visit our Website from a shared computer or a computer in an internet cafe, we strongly recommend that you log off after each session. If you do not want the shared computer to remember you and/or your credentials, you will need to remove cookies and/or the history of your website visits.

### Marketing Purposes

You agree that we may use the information collected by us to send you offers, whether personalised or not, or to contact you by telephone regarding products or Services offered by PataUza or companies of the eBay Group.

We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our Services and functionalities.

When you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can, where applicable, change your preferences in your MyPataUza account, or follow the unsubscribe link in the marketing communication you received.

### Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

We cannot modify your personal information or account information. You can modify your own information by logging into your MyPataUza account.  
When you place a classified ad, you may not be able to change your listing or delete your message. If you want to close your account (where applicable) with us, please send us a request here. We will process your request within a reasonable period of time and process your personal information in accordance with applicable law.  
If your information is factually incorrect or incomplete or irrelevant for the purposes for which we process your information, you can request us to modify or delete your information.

### Protection and retention of your personal information

We protect your information by using technical and administrative security measures (such as firewalls, data encryption, and physical and administrative access controls to the data and servers) that limit the risk of loss, abuse, unauthorised access, disclosure, and alteration. Nevertheless, if you believe your account has been abused, please contact us through the Contact Form.

### Abuse and unsolicited commercial communications ("spam")

We do not tolerate abuse of our Website. You do not have permission to add other PataUza users to your mailing list (e-mail or postal) for commercial purposes, even if a user has purchased something from you, unless the user has given his explicit consent. If you notice that someone is abusing our Website (spam or spoof emails), please notify us.  
It is not allowed to use our member-to-member communication resources to send spam or content that violates our Terms of Use in any other way. For your security, we may scan messages automatically and check for spam, viruses, phishing and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content. We do not permanently store messages sent through these resources.
